You've taken a coding boot camp
and passed all of your exams,
but you haven't been able to get a job.
You see the layoffs
from Big Tech and wondering,
Are my skills already obsolete? Yes.
Yes they are.
And that's why
we created a Rust for the Resilient.
You've already proven that
you can learn how to code.
Now it's time to learn how to code
like it's 2023
and get a job with a Fortune 1000
by migrating to Rust, the language
adopted by groups
like Microsoft,
Facebook, Amazon, Cloudflare and Linux.
You'll become immediately
relevant to software development managers
who are rewriting their entire codebase.
Rust for the Resilient -
Take the entrance exam now
to see if you qualify.